#### Contact

mhdfarrukh@gmail.com 00971554541024 LinkedIn Profile

## Top Skills · See all

Banking · Retail Banking · Cross Selling · Credit · Branch Banking · Loans · Commercial Banking · Credit Risk · Trade Finance · Relationship Management

Accomplishments · See all

3 Languages

# Mohammad Farrukh

Banking officer

Dubai

## Summary

Experienced Sales Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the banking industry. Skilled in Portfolio Management, Banking, Credit Analysis, Branch Banking, and Credit. Strong sales professional with a 10 , 10+2 focused in commerce , economics from ST John ,s School D.L.W , Varanasi ..

## Experience

Senior Relationship Officer · MarkAl Group of Companies

June 2021 - Present (8 months) · Dubai, United Arab Emirates

Selling of Financial Products

Bancassurance Advisor · First Abu Dhabi Bank (FAB)

May 2020 - January 2021 (9 months) · Dubai, United Arab Emirates

Senior Relationship Officer · CBD[bankcard]

August 2018 - March 2020 (1 year 8 months) · Dubai, United Arab Emirates

Wealth Management Advisor · ENBD Bank

April 2015 - May 2018 (3 years 2 months) · Dubai, United Arab Emirates

Senior Relationship Officer · Noor Bank

January 2014 - March 2015 (1 year 3 months) · Dubai, United Arab Emirates

See all of Mohammad's experience

#### Education

Uttar Pradesh Technical university Lucknow

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Marketing (2006 - 2008)